The following content is provided under a
Creative Commons license. Your support will
help MIT OpenCourseWare continue to offer
high -quality educational resources for
free. To make a donation or to view
additional materials from hundreds of MIT
courses, visit MIT OpenCourseWare
at ocw .mit .edu. OK.
So I thought I'd begin today with, as we're
coming to the end of the focus on linear
algebra and moving on to a little
probability, a little more optimization,
and a lot of deep learning. So this was
my way of review to write down the big
factorizations of a matrix.
And so my idea, and I kind of enjoyed
it, is checking that the number of free
parameters, say, in l and u or in q and r
or each of those, that the number of free
parameters agrees with the number
of parameters in a itself, like n squared
usually. So a usually has n squared. And
then can we replace a? After we've computed
l and u, can we throw away a? Yes, because
all the information is in l and u. And it
fills that same n by n matrix. Well, that's
kind of obvious, because l is a lower
triangular. And the diagonal, all 1s
are not free parameters. And u is upper
triangular. And it's diagonal. The pivots,
those are free parameters. But can I just
write down the count? So I'll go through
each of these just quickly after I've
figured out how these are the building
blocks. So how many free parameters are
there in these two triangular matrices?
Well, I think the answer is 1 half n, n
minus 1, and 1 half n, n plus 1. That's
a familiar number. That's the sum of,
you recognize that as the sum of 1 plus
2 up to n. And you have one free, in the
upper triangular u, you've got one free
parameter up in the corner, two in the next
one. And as you're coming down, you end up
with n on the main diagonal. And they add
up to that. And you see that those two are
different by n, which is what we want. OK,
diagonal, the
answer is obviously n.
How about the eigenvector matrix? So this
whole exercise is like something I've never
seen in a textbook. And it's just, but for
me, it brings back all these key, really
the condensed course in linear algebra
is on that top line. So how many free
parameters in an eigenvector matrix?
OK, and of course, you're sort of thinking,
what's the rule for free parameters? So
my answer is going to be for the number of
free parameters. This is an n by n matrix
with the n eigenvectors in it. But there's
a certain freedom there. And what is that?
What freedom do we have in choosing the
eigenvector matrix? Every eigenvector
can be multiplied by a scalar. If x is an
eigenvector, so is 2x, so is 3x. So we
could make a convention that the first
component was always 1. Maybe that wouldn't
be the most intelligent convention in the
world. But it would show that that top row
of 1s were not to be counted. So I get n
squared minus n for that. Oh, yeah, well,
having done those two, let me look at this
one. Does that come out a total of n
squared? Yes, because the eigenvector x has
n squared minus n by this reasoning.
A little hokey reasoning that I just gave.
And then there are n more for the
eigenvalue matrix. And there's nothing left
for the inverse, because it's determined by
x. So do you see the count adding up to n
squared for those? Now, I left open the
orthogonal one. I think we kind of talked
about that when we met it. And it's a
little less obvious. But do you remember?
So I'm talking about an n by n orthogonal
matrix, Q. So how many free parameters in
column 1? That column is what we always
call Q1. Does it have n free parameters? Or
is there a condition that cuts that back?
There is a condition, right? And what's the
condition on the first column that removes
one parameter? It's normalized. Its length
is 1. So I only get n minus 1 from the
first column. And now, if I move over to
the second column, how many free parameters
there? Again, it's a unit vector. But
also, it is orthogonal to the first. So two
rules got imposed, and two parameters got
removed. So this is n minus 2. And then
finally, whatever. So I think that that sum
of these guys is exactly the same that we
had up here. I think it's also 1 half n, n
minus 1, or 1 half n squared minus n. Yeah.
Yeah. So not as many as you might think,
because the matrix is size n squared. Now,
can I use those? Because these are like the
building blocks. Can I just check these?
Let's see. I'll just go along the list. L
times U. So L had this, and U had that. And
when I add those, it adds up to n squared,
right? The minus cancels the plus. And the
half n squared twice gives me n squared. So
good for that one. What about QR? Well,
R is upper triangular, like so. And then Q,
oh yeah. We just got it right there. So
for Q times R, it's that plus that, again,
adding to n squared. Good for that one. n
squared for that one. This one we just did.
n squared minus n in x. n on the diagonal,
total n squared. What about this guy?
What about the bigger, really fundamental
one that I would normally write the matrix
as S instead of A to remind us that
the matrix here is symmetric. So I'm not
expecting n squared for a symmetric matrix.
Oh, I should have put that on my list.
What's the count for
a symmetric matrix?
So because this is an S here. So I'm
not expecting to get n squared. I'm only
expecting to get the number of,
symmetric S. What's the number of free
parameters that I start with that I hope
will reappear in Q and lambda?
What's the deal for
a symmetric matrix?
Let's see. I'm free to choose. Is it the
same count as this? Yeah, because I'm free
to choose the upper triangular part and the
diagonal, but I'm not free to choose the
lower. So I'd say that's 1 half n times n
minus 1. And plus 1, sorry. The diagonal's
in there. OK. So do I get that total, 1
half of n squared plus n, from these guys?
Well, I probably do. The diagonal guy gives
me n. And that's a Q, which is my other
favorite number there. And when I add that
to that, that becomes a plus sign. And I'm
good. Yeah. You see how I enjoyed doing
this. Right. But I'm near the end. But the
last one is kind of not well known.
OK. Q times S. Do you remember that
factorization?
Polar decomposition. It's an orthogonal
times a symmetric. And it is often used in
engineering as a way to decompose a
displacement or strain matrix. Anyway, Q
times S. And it actually is very, very
close to the SVD. And I have friends who
say, better to compute QS than the SVD, and
then just move along. Anyway, Q times S.
So Q is this guy.
And S, what's S?
Symmetric. That's this guy.
So that's Q. Let me write that letter Q and
S so I don't lose it. What do those add up
to? And squared. Happy. So finally, the
SVD. Finally, the SVD. What's the count?
Well, now I've got rectangular stuff in
there. So I'm ready for this one. And I
have to think a little bit.
And we may have done this. So let's suppose
that M is less or equal M. Suppose that.
Yeah. Otherwise, we would just transpose
and look at the SVD. So let's say M less or
equal N. So let's
say it's got full rank.
And what's the largest rank that the matrix
can have? M, clearly. Full rank M. So the
SVD will be M by M. Let's remember the U,
the sigma, and the V transpose. This will
be M by N. And this will be N by N for the
full scale SVD. And if the rank is equal to
M,
then I really expect to get, I expect it
to add up to the total. The original A has
MN, right? It's
an M by N matrix.
The matrix A is M by N with M less or equal
N giving me these things. So it has MN
parameters.
So do we get M times N from this? I hope we
do. I know how many we get from sigma. How
many? What's the count for sigma? M. And
what's the count for V? So that's an N by
N. And what's the count for U? OK. Yeah.
That's their orthogonal matrices. So I
should be able to go up to that line. This
was an M by M one. So that's, is that a
half N, N minus 1? Am I copying
that correctly out of this circle there?
That's an M by M orthogonal matrix. Oh, but
I have to write M. That was foolish. OK.
M, M. Yeah, because that matrix is of size
M. So that's an M. And then I have that.
And then I have whatever V transpose
N by N. Oh, what's the deal in there? Do
I want all of the 1
half N, N minus 1?
Oh, god. I thought I'd
got this straight. Now to C.
No, I'm not.
Yes. And find out what I should say. Well,
students have been known to do this too.
Let's see. Well, let's try to think anyway.
So I have this N by N orthogonal matrix.
So first, it could be any orthogonal
matrix. Yeah. But is it only the first M
columns that I really need? The rest I
could just throw away. So let me try to
imagine that it's just the first. Well,
then I won't have any N in here. So maybe I
better take a half N. Help.
Oh. Oh, yes. Of course. Ha.
Only M columns that matter.
Everybody sort of now understands that
SVD. We've got the rank as M. Don't forget
that. Then the first R, the first M columns
of V are important. Those are the singular
vectors that go with non -zero singular
values that really matter. And the rest
really don't matter. So I'm going to just,
I have to count how many. So sorry. V, the
important part of V, has
how many?
Only M columns. But it's an N by N matrix.
And those columns are orthogonal. So the
answer is not MN for this guy. I have to
go through this foolish reasoning again. I
have N minus 1 plus N minus
2 plus so on plus N minus M.
There were N minus 1 parameters in the
first orthogonal vector or unit vector, N
minus 2 in the second one, up to N minus
M in the third. And then V has some more
columns that are coming really from a null
space that are not important. I believe
this is the right thing to do. I'm hoping
you agree. And now I'm hoping even more
that those add up to M times N.
OK. I have a half N. Oh, I really have to
total this thing. OK, this had M terms. So
there's M of these Ns. And then I have to
subtract off 1 plus 2 plus 3 up to M. And
so what am I subtracting off? What's
that sum, 1 plus 2 plus 3 stopping at M?
It's one of these guys, 1 half. Is it 1
half M, M plus 1? Yeah, 1 half M, M plus 1.
Sorry, 1 half M, M plus 1. I was supposed
to enjoy this. And now I'm a little
nervous. But OK, so I believe that that is
that. OK, well, we have the MN. That's a
good sign that we're shooting for. So
does the rest of it add to nothing? Well, I
guess, yeah, I guess it does. When I put
these two together, I have 1 half M, M plus
1. And then I'm subtracting it
away again. So I get MN. Hooray.
Well, had to happen, or we wouldn't. Before
I raise that board and consign that to
history, is there, should I pause a little
more minute? This will be, like I'm hoping,
a one -page appendix to the notes and
the book. Yeah, but I do have one more
count to do. And then I'm good with this
review and ready to move onward to the
topic of saddle points and ready to move
onward after that. Well, I'll say a little
bit about the next lab homework that I'm
creating. And then our next topic will be
like covariance matrices. A little
statistics this week. And then we get a
week off to digest it, and then come back
for gradient descent and deep learning and
those things. OK, everybody happy with
that? So what's my final question? My final
question is the SVD for any
matrix
of rank R. So it's
an M by N matrix,
but the rank is only R. That's a natural
question. How many parameters are there in
the rank R matrix?
And we may even have touched on this
question. And I have two ways to answer it.
And one way is the SVD. So let me, and
that'll be similar to what I just pushed up
there. So if the rank is R, the SVD of this
typical rank R matrix will be u sigma v
transpose. But u, now this is like the
condensed thing where I've thrown away
stuff that's automatically 0. Because if
the rank is only R, like if the rank was 1,
suppose the rank was 1. Then I'd have
one column times one sigma times one row,
right? And I could do that count
for R equal 1. Now I have R columns.
And I can do that count for M by R. The
sigma is diagonal, of course. So I'm going
to get R numbers out of that. And this
one is now R by N. In other words, maybe I
should save this little bit here that was
helpful. But now I've got M is reduced to
R. So I believe that if I count these
three, I'll get the right number of
parameters. So I've got the right number of
parameters for a rank R matrix. And that's
not so obvious. Because the rank R matrices
are not a, we don't have a subspace. If I
add a rank R matrix to another rank R
matrix, well, the rank could be as big as
2R and probably will be.
So
it's a little interesting to get your hands
on matrices of rank R. They're kind of a
thin, like a, well, a math person would
call it a manifold, some kind of a surface
within matrix space. Have you ever thought
about matrix space? So that's a vector
space. Because we can add matrices. We
can multiply them by constants. We can take
linear combinations. So we could call them
vectors if we like. That would be a vector
space of M by N matrices. What would be
the dimension of that space? So the vector
space of all 3 by 4 matrices, that has
what dimension? 12. Because you've got 12
numbers to choose. And it is a space
because you can add. Now if I say 3 by 4
matrices of rank 2,
I don't have a space anymore. That word
space is seriously preserved for meaning
vector space, meaning I can take
combinations. But if I take a rank 2 matrix
plus a rank 2 matrix, I'm not. So it's
sort of a surface within 12D, the 3 by 4
matrices of rank 2. And we're about to find
the dimension of that surface. Does your
mind sort of visualize a surface in 12
dimensions? Yeah. Yeah, well, give it a
shot anyway. But that surface could be 11
dimensional, so to speak. Meaning locally,
it wouldn't have to be an 11 dimensional
plane going through the origin. In fact, it
wouldn't go through the origin because the
origin won't have rank R. So it's some kind
of a surface. And maybe it's got some
different pieces. Probably some smart
person knows what that surface looks like.
But we're just going to find out something
about its number of parameters, its local
dimension. Well, I know that this answer is
R. Because I've got R sigmas. And this one
I'm pretty good at. But now it's R by N. So
it's instead of here, R was M. But now down
here, R is R. So I think it's RN minus 1
half.
What's that? Is that an M? So
now it's an R, R plus 1, I think. I think.
And what about the U? So U is going to
be similar, except instead of the N here,
we've got an M. So I think for U, we'll
have M minus 1 plus M minus 2 plus. So let
me write it here. M minus 1. So U, I'm
talking about U here. It's got R columns.
The first one has M minus 1, because I
throw away 1, because it's a unit vector,
up to M minus R. That's its R -th column.
And now, so what does that add up to? Well,
I put all the M's together. So that's RM.
Or let me say MR. And then I'm subtracting
on 1 plus 2 plus 3 up to R. Now tell me
again what that adds up to. 1 plus 2 plus 3
stop at R. That's what we had here. And
we've got it for V. And we've got it again
here. Minus 1 half R, R plus 1. Are you OK
with that? And now I just want to add them
up. So I have MR. And I have NR. And then
I have two of these. So let me get it here.
MR and NR. And now I have to look at it.
So MR, check. MR, check. Now I have two of
these guys. So they combine into R squared
plus R. And then I R squared. Yeah, minus R
squared plus R. Sorry. They combine into
minus R squared plus R. And then here is a
R coming in with a plus. I
think we have a minus R squared.
And that is the right answer. Yeah. OK.
So I took a bit longer than I intended. But
this is a number that's sort of
interesting. I mentioned saddle points
separately from maxima and minima just
because they are definitely not as easy to
work with. You understand what I mean
by saddle points? The matrices involved are
not positive definite.
They're not negative. They're not negative.
They're not, well, those would go with
maxima and minima. But we're looking in
between. So saddle points. OK. Well, I'll
get going on those. OK. I sort of realized
that there are two main sources of saddle
points.
One of them is when I have problems that,
when I, let's say I minimize. So this will
be the constraint. The saddle points that
come from the constraint. So Lagrange is
going to be responsible for these saddle
points. So we might have some minimum
problem, like minimize some positive
definite thing. And of course, if we don't
say any more, the minimum is 0. Right?
Because otherwise it's positive. But we're
going to put on constraints, Ax equal
b. So this is the classical constrained
optimization problem. Quadratic cost
function, linear constraints. We could
solve this exactly. But let's just see
where a saddle point is going to arise. So
this S is positive definite. But now how do
we deal with that problem? Well, Lagrange
said what to do. Lagrange
said look at the Lagrangian.
OK. He introduced lambda. So this x is in n
dimensions. That's an n by n matrix. But I
have m constraints. So
the matrix A is m by n.
I have m constraints. And then I'm going to
follow the rules and introduce m Lagrange
multipliers.
That's an m.
And then the neat part of the Lagrange. And
what is this? Well, I take the function.
And then I introduce, remember lambda is a
vector now. Not just a number. We had some
application where it was just one
constraint. But now I have m constraints.
So I take lambda. So lambda transpose times
Ax minus b. And the plus or the minus sign
here is not important. I mean, you can
choose it, because that'll determine the
sign of lambda. But either way, it's
correct. OK. So we've introduced a function
that now depends on
x and also on lambda.
And they multiply each other. And my point
is that Lagrange says take the derivatives
with respect to x and lambda. So that's the
cool thing that he's contributed. He says
if you only create my function, now you can
take x derivative and lambda derivative.
That'll give you n equations from this
one, from the x derivative, and m equations
from the lambda derivative. It'll be n
plus m. It'll determine the good x and the
lambda. But I'm saying that's all true and
all important. But I'm saying that the x
and that pair x lambda will be a saddle
point of this function. This function has
saddle points. It's not a maximum.
OK. Let's just take the derivatives and see
what we get. So the derivatives
with respect to x, d by the x. x is now a
vector. So I really should say the
gradient in the x direction. I get Sx.
And here, the derivative
with respect to x.
That is A transpose lambda, because this is
the dot product of A transpose lambda with
x. You know I've put parentheses around it
and followed the transpose rule. So that's
the dot product of A transpose lambda with
x. It's linear in x. So its derivative is
just A transpose
lambda. And that's 0.
And now I take the other
one, the lambda derivative.
The lambda derivative, this doesn't depend
on lambda. The lambda derivative is just Ax
minus B. It brings
back the constraints.
So that's pretty simple. Now, it doesn't
even require much thought, because you just
know the constraints are coming back.
And of course, B should be put over on this
side, because it's a constant. So there we
see two A block. We see a very important
class of problems. And the matrix we're
seeing, we could write this in block matrix
form, S minus A transpose. Oh, I'm going to
change that to a plus, because I'm more of
a plus person. OK. A transpose and A. Yeah.
Yeah. When I took the derivative of this,
the lambda, I didn't put the minus sign in
here. And I didn't want to. So let's make
it a plus. A. And then
there's nothing there. And the x
and the lambda and the 0 and the B.
That is the model of a constrained minimum,
a minimum problem with constraints.
Here is quadratic. And the constraints are
linear. It's in course 6, it's everywhere,
constantly appearing as the simplest
model. And my point today is just that the
solution x lambda,
that total solution, the x together with a
lambda, that that is a saddle point of the
Lagrangian function L. It's a saddle point,
not a minimum. It's sort of a minimum in
the x direction,
because this is positive definite. That
makes that, as a function of x, it's going
up.
But somehow the appearance of lambda makes
this matrix indefinite. It starts positive
definite, but it has this A transpose A and
that 0. It couldn't be posi - actually, if
I look at that matrix, I see it's not
positive definite. What do I see? Why do I
say that immediately? When I look at
that matrix, it's not a positive definite
matrix, because
when I see that 0 on the diagonal, that
shoots positive definite. Couldn't be. Take
as an example s equal 3, 1, and
1, 0. Take that matrix. Just random.
I made it 2 by 2 instead of size m plus
n. Do you see, how do I know that the
eigenvalues of that matrix, 1 is plus and
1 is minus? The determinant is negative.
So that tells me right away that 1 is plus
and 1 is minus. Thanks. Yes, yes, yes. The
determinant is negative. And somehow here,
the determinant is similar. Calculation
would produce A transpose A or something
with the minus, because I'm going this way.
Well, I could do
better than that.
But you saw the point. That matrix, that
simple example of this is has eigenvalues
of both signs. Let me just quickly say,
and I'll put it in the notes or in that
chapter. I guess all this is coming is
still 3 .2. That was originally 4 .2. And
you'll see it. So what do I want to say?
I'd like to say that that example is pretty
convincing to me, that these
KKT matrices, if you talk to people
in optimization, that's Karush, Kuhn, and
Tucker, three famous guys. And these are
the KKT conditions that they derived
following Lagrange. And my point is, and
this is a typical sort. So it's an
indefinite matrix. I believe it has,
if I do elimination, yeah, tell me this.
This is a good way to look at it. I do
elimination on this one or on this one?
Well, suppose I do elimination there. What
is the first pivot? 3, positive. So now
let me turn down to here. What if I do
elimination on this block matrix? Then
I start up here, and that first pivot is
positive again, right? This S is a
positive definite matrix. Don't forget.
The first two pivots will all be positive,
because the first n pivots, you're working
away in this corner. And if you're only
thinking about the first n, this corner is
sized n by n. Then you don't even see a.
You're doing some subtractions. And I'll do
those. But the pivots themselves are all
coming from S. And S is positive definite.
So we know that one of the tests for a
positive definite matrix is all pivots are
positive. So I think all n of the first
pivots will be positive. And when we use
them, let's just see what
happens when we use them.
So here is the KKT
matrix that I start with.
And what do I end up with?
Well, really what I'm doing is I'm
multiplying that block row by something and
subtracting to kill that a. So these
rows, well, near enough. Let me do block
elimination. Block elimination is easier.
I don't have to write down all little tiny
numbers. So I just want to multiply
this row by something. Tell me what. And
subtract from this second row. Suppose
there are numbers or letters. I guess they
are letters. What do I multiply
that first row by and subtract?
Let's see. If these were just little tiny
numbers, as like in 3, 1, 1, 0, what do I
multiply that row by and subtract from
this? I multiply by a over S, right? I do
multiply by a over S, which puts an a
there. And then I subtract. So here I'll
multiply by a over S. But these are
matrices. So I multiply by a S inverse,
right? When I multiply by a S inverse times
this S, I get a. And then I subtract. And
I get the 0. And when I multiply by this
guy and subtract, I get minus, because I'm
subtracting, this thing
minus a S inverse a transpose.
That was block elimination,
which just, in other words, is just,
you know, you've learned
about 2 by 2 matrices.
And then stuff. Now I'm just doing it with
blocks instead of single numbers. But you
see, this produced those positive pivots.
And what can you tell me about that matrix?
What can you tell me about the signs or
the eigenvalues or whatever of this matrix?
Suppose S was the identity. What could
you tell me about minus a A transpose?
Minus a A transpose. And my voice should
emphasize that minus. That matrix there is
negative definite. So all the next set of
m pivots that come from here will all be
negative. So I
get m, or rather n,
n positive and n
negative pivots.
And then I remember that the pivots
actually have the same sign as the
eigenvalues. That's just a beautiful fact.
We know that for positive definite ones,
the eigenvalues are all positive.
The pivots are all positive. But it's even
better than that. If we have some mixture
for the signs of the pivots, that tells us
the signs of the eigenvalues. That's
a really neat fact. So I'll just write that
down. Signs, plus and
minus signs of pivots give
us the plus and minus
signs of the eigenvalues.
So I've sneaked in a nice matrix theorem
for symmetric matrices. This is symmetric
matrices.
That's what I wanted to say about
constraints and saddle points coming from
there. And then I now want to say something
about constraints and not constraints now.
I'm going to look at the second source
of saddle points. So these will be saddles
from this remarkable
function that we know.
So I now have a symmetric matrix. S could
be even positive definite. Usually it is
here. Do you know what the name for r
is? It's a ratio or a quotient. It's named
after somebody starting with r. Who's that?
Rayleigh, right? It's Rayleigh quotient.
And what is the largest value,
possible value, of the Rayleigh quotient?
We've seen this idea. It is the maximum
value of that Rayleigh quotient, of that
ratio, is lambda max. Right, lambda 1, the
biggest one. And the x that does it is the
eigenvector.
So max is lambda 1 and at x equal q1.
Because q1 transpose Sq1 over q1 transpose
q1. So I'm plugging in this winner. And
Sq1 is lambda 1 q1, right? It's the first
eigenvector. And so a lambda
1 comes out. So I get lambda 1.
I know everything about that. And what I
know is, if I put in any x, what do I know?
If I put in any x whatever and look at this
number, what do I know about that number?
It's smaller than lambda 1. Or it might hit
lambda 1, but it's not bigger. That's why
maxima are easy. You put in any vector, and
you know what's happening. You know it's
not above the max, obviously.
And what about the min?
That's equally simple, of course. It's at
the bottom. So what would be the minimum of
that, Rayleigh, of that quotient, if I was
looking for what eigenvector and eigenvalue
will I find when I look at the bottom? Of
this, I will find lambda n, the last guy,
lambda min.
And the winning x will be its eigenvector.
And again, this stuff will equal lambda n.
So that's easy. I know that if
I put in any vector whatever,
just choose any vector in n dimensions
and compute r of x, what do I now also know
about that r of that vector?
It's greater than lambda n,
below the max, above the min. But now, if I
put in, now what about the other lambdas?
Well, the point is that those are saddle
points. The beautiful thing about this
Rayleigh quotient is, its derivative
equals 0 right at the saddle point. At the
eigenvectors. And its value at the
eigenvectors is the eigenvalue. So I have,
you see what I'm saying? I have lambda 1
here, a max, lambda n here, a min. And in
between, I have a bunch of other lambdas,
which are saddle points. And if I put an x
in to r of x and look to see what happens,
I have no idea whether I'm on this side,
below it, or this side above lambda i. So
the saddle points are more difficult and
take a little more patience. So that's
the other source of saddle points. And I,
so these are, so let me just emphasize
again what I'm saying. Lambda at x equal
qk, I have some number, the r of x has some
number of positive eigenvalues and some
number of negative ones for the
things above and below qk. OK.
Follow up on the saddle point part of the,
on the details of this picture. I might,
that'll be in the notes. And I might come
back to it at the very start of next time.
But I will, before that, you will have
the lab number three. And then I think we
should discuss it. Because
I haven't done this lab.
It's intended to give you some feeling for
overfitting, and also intended to give you
a little introduction to deep learning.
And so I'll get it to you, and we can talk
about it Wednesday. And again, it won't
be due until the Wednesday after break. OK,
thanks. So I'll see
you Wednesday.